A Guide to the Kathleen Booth Williams Papers, 1860-ca. 1982
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Kathleen Booth Wiilliams Papers, 1860-ca. 1982
The Library of Virginia
33430
12.7 cubic feet, 23 index card files
Williams, Kathleen Booth, 1893-1982
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Estate of Kathleen Booth Williams, 1988.
Biographical Information
Kathleen Booth was born 24 November 1893 and married Edward Burton Williams on 25 October 1917. She was an active genealogist and author of a number of genealogical publications on Amelia, Goochland, Louisa, and Pittsylvania Counties, Virginia. She died on 27 March 1982.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1860-1982, of Kathleen Booth Williams (1893-1982) consisting of family correspondence, arranged alphabetically by correspondent and then chronologically; general correspondence arranged alphabetically by correspondent with separate folders for major correspondents; client correspondence and research arranged alphabetically by client with notations on family research; patriotic society applications and supporting documentation; Genealogical notes arranged alphabetically by family; county record abstracts arranged alphabetically by Virginia county and then alphabetically by record type with other state records at the end.
Marriage record abstracts arranged alphabetically by Virginia county with other states filed next, followed by miscellaneous or multiple county abstracts; cemetery, census, church, and military records, newspaper abstracts, subject files are arranged alphabetically within each record series; printed materials and ephemera; photographs.
Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, scrapbooks, 1957, 1960-1965, of "Climbing the Family Tree: Genealogy Questions and Answers," by Hugh S. Watson, Jr., and scrapbooks, 1960-1971, of Coats of Arms are available on microfilm (Misc. reel 1087). There is also a large series of labeled index card files, principally marriage records.
Index Cards files are listed at the end of this finding aid.
Contents List
- Kathleen Booth Williams Papers, 1860-ca. 1982. (Box 1-13)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Inez Acree (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Business/accounts (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: C. S. Booth (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Florence Booth (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: P. B. Booth (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Peter L. Booth (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Sue Booth (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: William H. Booth (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: May Burton (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: A. L. Duncan (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Annie (Duncan) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Lula M. Duncan (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Willie Duncan (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Fannie Hancock (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: F. N. Hancock (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: H. H. Hancock (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Kate Hancock (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: G. W. Hancock (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: W. S. Hancock (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: E. G. Moseley (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Bettie A. Potter (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Eliza Wooding (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Mary Wooding (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: W. C. Wooding (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Aunt Alice (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Cousin Walter (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: Miss Pat (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Booth Family Correspondence: F-W, unidentified (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Mollie Allen (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Mrs. Mollie Allen (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Annie K. Booth (Mrs. Williams) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Charles L. Booth (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Charles L. Booth, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Louise Booth (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: A. L. Duncan (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Annie L. Duncan (Mrs. Booth) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Evelyn M. Duncan (Lula) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Julia Duncan (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Kate L. Duncan (Mrs. Keeney) (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Martha B. Duncan (Mattie) (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Sallie W. Duncan (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Teacher's contract (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Mrs. Sarah E. Duncan (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: W. E. Duncan (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: F. S. Hancock (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Frances S. Hancock (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: H. H. Hancock (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: J. H. Hancock (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: C. Edward Holland (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Sallie Holland (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: Mabel Keeney (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Duncan-Booth Family Correspondence: B-T, unidentified (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Transcipts of Correspondence: 1860, 1866, 1868 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence: A (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence: Ba-Bol (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence: Boo-Bur (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. W. D. Bond, Sr. (Verlan), Stamp Family (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. Carlson F. Booth (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. John N. Booth (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence: Talmadge Booth (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence: Philip Burton (Burton family) (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence: C (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. Curran W. Casho[?] (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. Ben D. Currie (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence: D (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence: Tom Duncan (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence: E (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. Donald D. Ellis (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence: Mildred O. Eubank (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence: F (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence: Pearl S. Freeman (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence: G (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. David I. Garrett (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence: Maurice Kirby Gordon (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence: H (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence: Robert B. Hancock (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence: Frances Harris (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence: Mildred Cox Hodson (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. Walter J. Hodson (Noma C.) (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence: T. P. Hughes Jr. (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence: I (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence: J (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence: K (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. W. F. Kesteloo (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence: George H. S. King (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence: Lucille S. Krisch (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. H. A. Knorr (Kitty) (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence: L (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. James R. Lindsay (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. M. V. Love (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence: Ma-McNicol (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence: McQueen-Mudd (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence: Robert L. Mahon (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. Emma R. Mathen (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence: Francis C. McKenna (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. W. R. McKenna (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. L. Moton Menefee (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence: N (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence: O (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence: P (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence: V. L. Peddicord (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence: E. H. Pettibon (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence: Lucille C. Price (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence: Q (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence: R (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence: Mrs. Vera M Ryker (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence: S (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence: Charlotte Sheffer (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence: Eileen Sheffield (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence: Mildred W. Steltzner (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Correspondence: Etta S. Stokes (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Correspondence: T (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Correspondence: Helen M. Turner (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Correspondence: U (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Correspondence: V (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Correspondence: Wa-Wile (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Correspondence: Will-Wo (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Correspondence: J. T. Wood (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Correspondence: Bobby Wooding (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Correspondence: Frank Preston Wooding (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Correspondence: Nathaniel H. Wooding (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Correspondence: Y (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Correspondence: Brian L. Young (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Correspondence: Z (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Correspondence: Unidentified (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: R. W. Alexander/Jennings Family (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: A. R. Bates/Bates Family (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. J. F. Beamis/James Family (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. J. M. Benson/Hancock Family (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. J. M. Benson/Maddox Family (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: R. E. Blevins/Burnett-Blevins Families (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. M. F. Bird/Harris Family (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. A. E. Brown/Nelson-Allen Families (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. W. D. Bond/Gates-Ward Families (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. R. P. Burdette/Epps Family (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. C. Cassingham/Owen Family (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: M. C. Collie/Change-Dodson Families (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: M. L. Cooley/Floyd-Summers-Hurst-Davis Families (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. F. S. Craig/Shelton Family (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: H. K. Crews/Gorman-Humphries Families (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: E. Deegan/Marshall Family (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: I. Farmer/Farmer Family (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. V. G. Gillette/Welborn Family (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. J. Hughes/Clift Family (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: D. T. Irby/Irby Family (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: R. C. Jones/Dodson Family (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. E. H. Kennard/Johnson-Harrison-Fitzgerald Families (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: G. Knowles/Sullivan Family (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. M. V. Love/City Family (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: R. L. Mahon/Mahon Family (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: M. McWhorter/Parham Family (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. R. A. Miller/Turley Family (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Dr. R. D. Mudd/Folder 1 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Dr. R. D. Mudd/Folder 2 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: F. E. Parker/Farmer-Burton-Wiles Families (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: M. G. Price/Price Family (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. J. L. Roberston/Robertson Family (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. F. I. Robinson/Robertson Family (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. V. M. Ryker/Boxley Family (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. E. R. Smith/Robinson-England-Holland Families (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: V. Stimson/Stimson Family (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. A. E. Werner/Cole Family (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. O. White/Hudnall Family (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. W. K. Whetstone/Allen Family (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. W. A. White/Green Family (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. W. A. White/Moor(e)-Green-Keesee Families (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Client Correspondence and Research: Mrs. S. R. Williams/Ayers Family (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Patriotic Society Applications and Supporting Documentation (Box 5, Folder 168-172)
  - Genealogical Notes: Abston Family (Box 6, Folder 173)
  - Genealogical Notes: Adams Family (Box 6, Folder 174)
  - Genealogical Notes: Adkins Family (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - Genealogical Notes: Allen Family (Box 6, Folder 176)
  - Genealogical Notes: Amos Family (Box 6, Folder 177)
  - Genealogical Notes: Anderson Family (Box 6, Folder 178)
  - Genealogical Notes: Arrington Family (Box 6, Folder 179)
  - Genealogical Notes: Austin Family (Box 6, Folder 180)
  - Genealogical Notes: Baker Family (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - Genealogical Notes: Ballenger Family (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Genealogical Notes: Banks Family (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Genealogical Notes: Barksdale Family (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Genealogical Notes: Bates Family (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Genealogical Notes: Bayse Family (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Genealogical Notes: Beauford Family (Box 6, Folder 187)
  - Genealogical Notes: Bedford Family (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - Genealogical Notes: Bell Family (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - Genealogical Notes: Berger Family (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - Genealogical Notes: Blackwell Family (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - Genealogical Notes: Blades Family (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - Genealogical Notes: Blanks Family (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Genealogical Notes: Blevins Family (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Genealogical Notes: Board Family (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Genealogical Notes: Bobbitt Family (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Genealogical Notes: Bolling Family (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Genealogical Notes: Booth Family (Box 6, Folder 198-203)
  - Genealogical Notes: (Beverly) Booth Family (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Genealogical Notes: (Christopher S.) Booth Family (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Genealogical Notes: Booth-Keen Families (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Genealogical Notes: Bostick Family (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Genealogical Notes: Boswell Family (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Genealogical Notes: Boxley Family (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Genealogical Notes: Bradley Family (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Genealogical Notes: Branch Family (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Genealogical Notes: Brown Family (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - Genealogical Notes: Brown-Dabney Families (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - Genealogical Notes: Burch Family (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - Genealogical Notes: Burnett Family (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Genealogical Notes: Burrus Family (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Genealogical Notes: Burton Family (Box 6, Folder 217-218)
  - Genealogical Notes: Butterworth Family (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Genealogical Notes: Cabell Family (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Genealogical Notes: Calland Family (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Genealogical Notes: Camden Family (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Genealogical Notes: Carter Family (Box 6, Folder 223-224)
  - Genealogical Notes: Cash Family (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Genealogical Notes: Cashion Family (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Genealogical Notes: Chaney Family (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Genealogical Notes: Chappell Family (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Genealogical Notes: Chattin Family (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Genealogical Notes: Childress Family (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Genealogical Notes: Chilton Family (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Genealogical Notes: Christopher Family (Box 6, Folder 232-233)
  - Genealogical Notes: Christopher Family (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - Genealogical Notes: Christopher-Angell-Jacobus-Gower-Nicholas Families (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Genealogical Notes: Christopher-Clark-Collins Families (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Genealogical Notes: Clark Family (Box 7, Folder 237)
  - Genealogical Notes: Clay Family (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - Genealogical Notes: Clement(s) Family (Box 7, Folder 239)
  - Genealogical Notes: Cliborne Family (Box 7, Folder 240)
  - Genealogical Notes: Coe Family (Box 7, Folder 241)
  - Genealogical Notes: Coke Family (Box 7, Folder 242)
  - Genealogical Notes: Coleman Family (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - Genealogical Notes: Coles-Bruce Family (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - Genealogical Notes: Cook Family (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Genealogical Notes: Corbin Family (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - Genealogical Notes: Cornelius Family (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - Genealogical Notes: Cox Family (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - Genealogical Notes: Cragin Family (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - Genealogical Notes: Crowley Family (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - Genealogical Notes: Crews Family (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - Genealogical Notes: Cunningham Family (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - Genealogical Notes: Davis Family (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - Genealogical Notes: Davis-Howell Family (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - Genealogical Notes: Dent Family (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Genealogical Notes: Dew Family (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Genealogical Notes: Dickson/Dixon Family (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - Genealogical Notes: Dillard Family (Box 7, Folder 258)
  - Genealogical Notes: Dodson Family (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - Genealogical Notes: Dortch Family (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Genealogical Notes: Duffer Family (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Genealogical Notes: Duncan Family (Box 7, Folder 262-266)
  - Genealogical Notes: Easley Family (Box 7, Folder 267-268)
  - Genealogical Notes: Echols Family (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - Genealogical Notes: Elam Family (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - Genealogical Notes: Eley Family (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - Genealogical Notes: Ellis Family (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Genealogical Notes: Epes Family (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - Genealogical Notes: Evans Family (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - Genealogical Notes: Farmer Family (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Genealogical Notes: Farrar Family (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - Genealogical Notes: Fish Family (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - Genealogical Notes: Fisher Family (Box 7, Folder 278)
  - Genealogical Notes: Fitzgerald Family (Box 7, Folder 279)
  - Genealogical Notes: FitzPatrick Family (Box 7, Folder 280)
  - Genealogical Notes: Floyd Family (Box 7, Folder 281)
  - Genealogical Notes: Fontaine Family (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - Genealogical Notes: Fowlkes Family (Box 7, Folder 283)
  - Genealogical Notes: Freeman Family (Box 7, Folder 284)
  - Genealogical Notes: Gaines Family (Box 7, Folder 285)
  - Genealogical Notes: Gammon Family (Box 7, Folder 286)
  - Genealogical Notes: Garrett Family (Box 7, Folder 287)
  - Genealogical Notes: Gates Family (Box 7, Folder 288)
  - Genealogical Notes: Gilbert Family (Box 7, Folder 289)
  - Genealogical Notes: Giles Family (Box 7, Folder 290)
  - Genealogical Notes: Gilliam Family (Box 7, Folder 291)
  - Genealogical Notes: Glascock Family (Box 7, Folder 292)
  - Genealogical Notes: Golson Family (Box 7, Folder 293)
  - Genealogical Notes: Gower Family (Box 7, Folder 294)
  - Genealogical Notes: Grasty-Clark-Lightfoot Families (Box 7, Folder 295)
  - Genealogical Notes: Green Family (Box 7, Folder 296)
  - Genealogical Notes: Haile/Hale Family (Box 8, Folder 297)
  - Genealogical Notes: Haines Family (Box 8, Folder 298)
  - Genealogical Notes: Haley Family (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hall Family (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hamilton Family (Box 8, Folder 301)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hancock Family (Box 8, Folder 302)
  - Genealogical Notes: Harris Family (Box 8, Folder 303)
  - Genealogical Notes: Harrison Family (Box 8, Folder 304)
  - Genealogical Notes: Harvey Family (Box 8, Folder 305)
  - Genealogical Notes: Harwell Family (Box 8, Folder 306)
  - Genealogical Notes: Harwood Family (Box 8, Folder 307)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hatcher Family (Box 8, Folder 308)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hawkins Family (Box 8, Folder 309)
  - Genealogical Notes: Haymes Family (Box 8, Folder 310)
  - Genealogical Notes: Haynes Family (Box 8, Folder 311)
  - Genealogical Notes: Helm Family (Box 8, Folder 312)
  - Genealogical Notes: Henderson Family (Box 8, Folder 313)
  - Genealogical Notes: Henley Family (Box 8, Folder 314)
  - Genealogical Notes: Herndon Family (Box 8, Folder 315)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hill Family (Box 8, Folder 316)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hines Family (Box 8, Folder 317)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hodnett Family (Box 8, Folder 318)
  - Genealogical Notes: Holland Family (Box 8, Folder 319-320)
  - Genealogical Notes: (Thomas) Holland Family (Box 8, Folder 321)
  - Genealogical Notes: Holland-Duncan-Booth Families (Box 8, Folder 322)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hollins Family (Box 8, Folder 323)
  - Genealogical Notes: Holloway Family (Box 8, Folder 324)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hook Family (Box 8, Folder 325)
  - Genealogical Notes: Holt Family (Box 8, Folder 326)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hopkins Family (Box 8, Folder 327)
  - Genealogical Notes: Howland Family (Box 8, Folder 328)
  - Genealogical Notes: Howson Family (Box 8, Folder 329)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hudgins Family (Box 8, Folder 330)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hudnall Family (Box 8, Folder 331)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hunnicutt Family (Box 8, Folder 332)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hunt Family (Box 8, Folder 333)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hunter Family (Box 8, Folder 334)
  - Genealogical Notes: Hurt Family (Box 8, Folder 335-336)
  - Genealogical Notes: Ingles Family (Box 8, Folder 337)
  - Genealogical Notes: Irby Family (Box 8, Folder 338)
  - Genealogical Notes: Jackson Family (Box 8, Folder 339)
  - Genealogical Notes: James Family (Box 8, Folder 340)
  - Genealogical Notes: Jamison-Akers Family (Box 8, Folder 341)
  - Genealogical Notes: Jefferson Family (Box 8, Folder 342)
  - Genealogical Notes: Jennings Family (Box 8, Folder 343)
  - Genealogical Notes: Jeter Family (Box 8, Folder 344)
  - Genealogical Notes: Johnson Family (Box 8, Folder 345)
  - Genealogical Notes: Johnston Family (Box 8, Folder 346)
  - Genealogical Notes: Jones Family (Box 8, Folder 347)
  - Genealogical Notes: Keeling Family (Box 8, Folder 348)
  - Genealogical Notes: Keen Family (Box 8, Folder 349)
  - Genealogical Notes: Keeney Family (Box 8, Folder 350)
  - Genealogical Notes: Keesee Family (Box 8, Folder 351)
  - Genealogical Notes: Kendricks Family (Box 8, Folder 352)
  - Genealogical Notes: Kent Family (Box 8, Folder 353)
  - Genealogical Notes: King Family (Box 8, Folder 354)
  - Genealogical Notes: Kirby Family (Box 8, Folder 355)
  - Genealogical Notes: Klander Family (Box 8, Folder 356)
  - Genealogical Notes: Knight Family (Box 8, Folder 357)
  - Genealogical Notes: Lake Family (Box 8, Folder 358)
  - Genealogical Notes: Lanier Family (Box 8, Folder 359)
  - Genealogical Notes: Lee Family (Box 8, Folder 360)